	tiv	

I will deliver a strong message by creating a change to improve our future. A future that allows people to have an obstacle-free path that allows unlimited growth. Therefore, I will dedicate my passion and ambition for problem-solving, analytical skills, and diverse and highly competent software engineering expertise in multiple fields to achieve this goal. Whatever it takes.

Education

King Fahd University of Petroleum & Minerals (KFUPM) ~ 5 years

Bachelor of Science, Software Engineering Sep 2016 → May 2021

Georgia Institute of Technology (GaTech) ~ 5 months

Exchange Program, Computer Science

Atlanta, GA, USA

Dhahran, KSA

Riyadh, KSA

Aug 2019 → Dec 2019

Experience

SAFCSP ~ 9 months

Axenda \sim 2 years

Software Engineer - Empower the Saudi workforce through diverse bootcamps Lead Instructor - Led a class of 25 students as part of the Tuwaiq 1000 initiative

Sep $2021 \rightarrow Jan 2022$ Remote

Mar $2020 \rightarrow Present$

Jan 2022 → Present

Founder & CEO - Lead 2-98 member building scalable tech products

Mohtwize \sim 2 months

Software Engineer - Worked as product architect and developer

Riyadh, KSA Aug 2021 \rightarrow Sep 2021

Udacity ~ 1.5 years

iOS Session Lead - Trained more than 100 students on iOS development

Remote + Dhahran, KSA Mar 2019 → Aug 2020

TechBench \sim 2 years

Member / Tech Lead - Introduced tech to people via workshops and hackathons

Dhahran, KSA Oct 2018 → Aug 2020

Sary ~ 5 months **Business Analyst** - Analyzed business processes for optimization and automation

Remote + Dammam, KSA Mar 2020 → Jul 2020

KFUPM ∼ 7 months

Database Systems Grader - Graded homeworks and helped students with projects Intro to Computing Grader - Wrote a script to grade homeworks faster

Dhahran, KSA

Jun 2019 → Aug 2019

Feb $2020 \rightarrow May 2020$

Tweetso ~ 9 months

iOS Developer - Developed two applications (Experto & Experto Partners)

Dhahran, KSA Nov 2017 → Jul 2018

Shahla ~ 8 years Alahsa, KSA

Family Business - Worked as a cleaner, salesperson, inventory clerk, manager, and IT

Sep $2008 \rightarrow \text{Aug } 2016$

Awards

First Place at Aramco's Wa'ed Hackathon **Top Three** at SAP-KAUST Hackathon

Dec 2018 Feb 2019

Volunteering

KFUPM Voluntary Work Unit

Volunteer - Helped society through various initiatives in a huge voluntary event

Dhahran, KSA Feb 2018, 2019, 2020

Dhahran, KSA

Trainer - Introduce Microsoft's micro-computer, the micro:bit, to children

Dhahran, KSA Dec 2017

Code.org

Trainer - Introduce programming to 402 young students throughout several workshops

Dec 2017

References Salah Adam, Database Systems Assistant Professor at KFUPM

adam@kfupm.edu.sa

Dania Abedaljawad, Learning Experience Design Manager at Udacity

dania.abedaljawad@udacity.com

Hussain Ali, Product Manager at Mohtwize

hussain@mohtwize.com